bizzclick.com 2019-05-20

# Privacy Policy - Bizzclick

At Bizzclick we believe that clear, transparent, and comprehensive privacy policies should be the main basis of any business functioning. 

We aim to make our customer’s experience safe and secure. During the process of information collection, processing, and storing we provide our users with total confidentiality, ensuring all our procedures also fully correspond to the current GDPR regulation. 

Please read these privacy policies carefully and stay well-informed about your fundamental privacy rights protection the types of the data we use, the cases when such data can be collected in details.. In case you have any questions regarding these privacy policies we recommend you to discuss them with your attorney. 

##  Segment I. General Information 

Bizzclick is happy to provide you with top-notch programmatic and direct trading services using which you can buy premium quality online inventory generating highest CPM, select among hottest mobile or desktop ad formats, and boost your ad campaign tuning it the way it is convenient for you. 

### Our business

We are intended to use "us", "we", and "our" in this policies to indicate the Bizzclick Corp party, the full-stack platform for programmatic advertising that provides highly technological services to its customers through OpenRTB protocol. 

Bizzclick Corp was founded in 2007 and has its main headquarter located in Miami, US. Since 2007, Bizzclick Corp has drastically grown its capacities and currently successfully implements the most cutting-edge solutions for CPM Advertising, Media, Publishing, Consulting, and Business Services. 

Bizzclick Corp treats your customer rights with respect and ensures that we deal with your personal data with due attention, striving to provide you with transparency considering your personal data usage. 

### Our Privacy Policies and GDPR compliance

Bizzclick Corp acknowledges the obligation to manage your personal data according to GDPR regulation adopted by EU on 25 May, 2018. Become acquainted with the personal data we can collect, for what purpose such can be processed, which technology we normally use for this, and what cookies can be used during your visit and use of the service by reading these privacy policies. 

These privacy policies also disclose the order in which we ensure your personal data protection, including the policies towards children. These policies are integral part of the user agreement that should be regarded by you with an equal attention. 

Bizzclick Corp processes the personal data of EU and non-EU based citizens alike, that’s why you need to read “The legal principles for EEA user rights processing” if you are EU citizen and your personal data is subject to GDPR protection. 

### Dealing with your user information: the legitimate basis

Please be aware, - we do not have the access to your personal information during the process of gathering, processing, and storing your impersonified user data. We also apply indirect technology to collect the customer data abstaining from any other existing measures of data collection. 

The data that you provide is collected automatically within the process of your interaction with our service or website. 

Our party is also not interested in gathering any particular sort of user data, only the one that will be necessary for the best quality service delivery and the enhanced convenience of our customer. 

Look up Segment II to find out about all possible instances when collecting your personal information can be considered necessary. 

Browse through Segment III to familiarize yourself with all possible types of the information that could be collected by our website during the session. Besides, we recommend you to inspect your official client agreement along with these privacy regulations. 

### The user information collected by vendors and clients

The automatic collection of some user data, the cookies, tags, pixels, and related technologies is applied by our clients and vendors in order to improve your personal user experience and reaching their own business goals. 

Your user information collected and applied by our clients helps them to evaluate the implementation of advertising and marketing campaigns, create the opportunity for better targeting, and provide you with offers that can be potentially interesting and useful for you. 

Applying such technologies can be necessary for our clients and vendors, however, since such technologies may belong to them, Bizzclick Corp cannot be seen as an accountable party for such technologies and all arising concerns and questions regarding them should be redirected to their owners. 

As well, the privacy policies of our clients, vendors, and other parties they collaborate with are out of our control. 

### Contact Us

Regarding all questions that may arise from reading these privacy policies, which are related to the processing, storage, and usage of your personal data, please contact us using following e-mail [support@bizzclick.com](mailto:support@bizzclick.com) or send your request to the following address: 

Bizzclick Corp  
1840 SW 22ND ST., PMB 4-1136 MIAMI, FL 33145  
Attn: Privacy Officer  

## Segment II. Collected user data: types of information

Personal data - the type of information that helps to identify the particular user. The format of such data may vary (for example, your name, email address, IP address or feedback that you leave on the website). 

Note, that we collect the pseudonymous user data exceptionally, meaning that it is not matched with your actual, non-digital personal information. The data that gets recorded by our website includes IP address of your computer, cookies, and several additional data types you can find in the list below. 

Please be sure you don’t provide any kind of the sensitive personal information in the comment section of our website, in case you have any questions or inquiries, please contact us directly or by email. Also, be sure that such information is not leaked from your website and not accidentally involved in the technological data processing. 

Most of the jurisdictions classify the user information we collect as pseudonymous, in some instances, we may also collect additional digital user footprints for jurisdictions located in EU. 

### The type of data we collect

  * System log files (IP address, browser type, domain names, time zone, the type of platform used (mobile/desktop), various data related to website interaction: exit and enter pages and URLs, search keywords applied, the number of clicks, landing pages you visited, on-banner clicks, file downloading, website forms filled, device ID and geo-location). 
  * Information provided by your browser: personal browser settings, browsing history, language. 
  * Device-related information: Unique device identifier, type of the operating system installed in device, the model of device, manufacturer, the date and the country of launch, (ISP) - your current service Internet provider. 
  * The data that belongs to the third-parties or our clients that represents the auditory segments, behavior, and interest-based data used for the ad targeting, aggregated statistics retrieved from DMPs, etc. 

### The procedure of data collection

We will collect only information that is necessary for the best quality service delivery, that data that no longer participates in the technological process gets permanently erased. The types of information that we collect includes: 

**Cookies.** Like other websites and services we use cookies in order to optimize our services and website operation. When you use our website, the information gets automatically collected and includes the following data (operating system, IP address, the web pages you click on, links that you used to access website, etc.)  
Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer (or other device) when you visit the website for the first time and allow us recognize your computer during the visit. The temporary cookies are erased from your device just after you leave the website, the permanent ones are stored on your PC until the moment you manually clear the cache. 

**HTML5 and local objects.** The local objects appear as a string of code that has equal algorithm to cookies, along with HTML5, local objects are able to gather larger information arrays. Note, if you clear your browser history and other configurations you also delete the local objects with HTML5. 

**The tags and pixels.** Pixels and tags are analytical tools which help to measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns for our clients. Attached to the web pages or the emails pixels help to analyze the behavior of the user. We use own pixels or the ones provided by our clients, subsequently syncing them that allows to refine the quality and consistency of the information obtained. 

**SDKs.** The tiny code strings that assist user data collection, SDKs are directly integrated into device, they measure how the user interacts with the device. 

**The identifiers of the mobile device.** Used to measure the performance of the inventory, assess how often user viewed an inventory. 

### The way we process personal information

We process personal user information in the full accordance with current laws and regulations. 

If Bizzclick Corp is the subject of any kind of corporate changes in the future, involving organizational, transformational events, etc., the user information will be lawfully transferred to the new information controller. 

For the purposes of conducting customer research, improving the analytics data, compiling the surveys and effectiveness reports we may require collecting additional information that will greatly assist us and will give us insights about the spheres that need improvement. 

Sharing the mentioned data with clients and contractors is also necessary for ensuring the effectiveness of technological process for parties but the data that gets gathered doesn’t uncover the real identity of the user. Subsegment for EEA users 

### The legal principles for EEA user rights processing

With the permission of current GDPR regulation we oblige ourselves to collect, process, and store personal information of EU citizens according to the recommended standards mentioned in legislation. 

Your legal consent for such information collection is the first and the most important basis without which we will not be able to manage your data accordingly. 

We guarantee EU-based citizens that their data will be treated, stored, and protected in accordance with GDPR standards. Important, the following data management rules can be only extended on EU citizens. In case you need to clarify certain aspects of this policy or want your consent to be withdrawn you will have to provide the legal prove your rights are subjected to GDPR protection. 

In case you have general questions regarding your personal information management consider contacting us by e-mail: [support@bizzclick.com](mailto:support@bizzclick.com)

### Consent withdrawal

We appreciate your fundamental right to decide how to handle your personal information, including the right to access, transfer it, provide the consent or withdraw it. That’s why we guarantee you such rights can and will be executed in case of necessity. Thus, according to laws you can withdraw the consent you granted us anytime you need. 

Remember, if you gave your legal consent for information processing to our client, you will also have to ask them directly to cancel such consent. In case it was a third-party app you provided consent through withdraw the consent directly from that application configuring app’s settings. 

If you are the user and you don’t want to receive personalized ads, turn off the consent in your Android, selecting “Opt out of Ads Personalization” or choose “Limit AD Tracking” on IOS. In case you didn’t find the option on your device model we recommend you to consult the device manufacturer. 

You will no longer receive personalized advertisements after you turn off the feature, same way, we will no longer gather, collect, process, and store your data. Receiving such consent withdrawal request we will also be obliged to notify about it our clients, who will have to erase your information and stop utilizing it for targeting purpose. 

In some minor legal cases, we will have to keep storing your information despite your actual consent withdrawal, the precedents for such cases are defined by the GDPR regulation. 

### Legitimate Interest

It is in the right of Bizzclick Corp to retain the access to user data in cases defined by the legitimate interests. The legitimate interest will be determined for every platform on the ad hoc basis.

### Data management rights of EU residents

If you belong to EU residents your personal user data is the subject of GDPR regulation. In order to familiarize yourself better with your current rights please read General Data Protection Regulation, chapter 3.

Our technological processes for your data collection, processing, and storing are limited and are only able to reach your impersonified data, however, in case you have additional requests for your right execution, don’t hesitate to let us know. 

Please also keep in mind, our business is currently located in US and our technology is not perfectly suited to fully match EEA standards. Extracting some information might be hindered by the technological process, in such case you will have to provide us with additional information so that we could match it and ensure it really belongs to you. 

### How we store user data of EU residents

We will store and share only information that is necessary for the best quality service delivery, that data that no longer participates in the technological process gets permanently erased. For the time we store your information on our servers we ensure its total safety with all possible organizational and technical protection measures. Read more about it in “Data Security” block below. 

### How we share user data of EU residents

  * With our clients. Your personal data is an integral part of the targeting process during the personalized ad delivery. We share such information with our clients to contribute to the better targeting process. Our clients may use either the user data accumulated on their own or the data collected on our side. 
  * With informational safety entities. To ensure fraud-free and safe experience for our clients and protect the information of users. 
  * Other service owners. Online advertisement typically involves many participants, - several DSPs, SSPs, and sometimes DMPs. For the mutual convenience, we might share the necessary user data with other contractors that maintain and take an important part in the smooth bidding process. 
  * With governmental entities. In case such information disclosure is required and is necessary for the investigation and prevention of fraud, illegal actions or any other case of the law violation. 

### Turning off targeted Advertising:

The aim of the targeted advertisement is to present a particular user the type of service that can potentially be interesting for him or her, taking into account user’s interests, behavioral data, and other statistics. Such type of advertisement is not irritating and can be useful for both parties - for the advertiser and the user. 

Respecting the fundamental right for the personal data management we provide you with the ability to turn off such advertisement. You can configure it in your device settings. 

On your IOS device choose “Limit AD Tracking”, for the Android-based gadget select “Opt out of Ads Personalization”. In case you didn’t find the option on your device model we recommend you to consult the device manufacturer. 

You will no longer receive the personalized advertisement after you turn off the feature, same way, we will no longer gather, collect, process, and store your data. 

Remember if you gave your legal consent for information processing to our client, you will also have to ask them directly to cancel such consent. In case it was a third-party app you provided consent to address this party directly or turn off the consent configuring app’s settings. 

### The principles of Data Safety

Bizzclick Corp uses the best standards of technical and operational information protection against the possible losses, misuse, leakage or destruction of your personal data. 

Taking into account all threats related to the information management we should notify you about the potential risks of every operation that takes place online. At the same time, we do our best to protect your personal data at the highest possible level, applying the best technology approved industry-wide and practicing the best data safety procedures. 

### Policies considering children

Our service should not be used by children or people under the age of 18 without the consent of their parents or legal supervisors. We either do not collect the personal information of people who haven’t reached the adulthood. If your child accidentally submitted such kind of information contact us and the issue will be resolved as soon as possible. 

## Segment III. The information that we collect through the website

Bizzclick Corp retains the right to amend this privacy policy from time to time so we recommend you to occasionally check for the updates. Amendments will enter into force on the date of their publication. Using our website you agree to the existing policies and every section of it automatically. 

### Identifiable information we collect

Our website doesn’t collect Identifiable information of any kind. Such type of data can only be required for creating your personal account. 

### Non-identifiable information we collect

When you first visit our website non-identifiable information about you aggregates automatically through cookies and includes (IP address, browser type, domain names, timezone, OS, the type of platform used (mobile/desktop), the type of Internet provider, etc. Such data helps us to get to know our customers better and customize site usage experience, making it more convenient. 

### IP address

Your IP address is a unique address of your device in the network used for finding, transferring, and receiving information from one computer to another. 

We collect your IP address for the purpose of service improvement, investigating the problems with servers, in case such take place. Your IP will be linked to your identifiable data after you set up an account with us. 

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer (or another device) when you visit the website for the first time and allow us to recognize your computer during the visit. The temporary/session cookies are erased from your device just after you leave the website, the permanent ones are stored on your PC until the moment you manually clear the cache. 

### Policies considering children

Our website should not be used by children or people under the age of 18 without the consent of their parents or legal supervisors. We also do not collect the personal information of people who haven’t reached the adulthood. If your child accidentally submitted such kind of information contact us and the issue will be resolved as soon as possible.
